http://www.membersourcecu.org/privacy-policy/

gt
Select LanguageChinese (Simplified)EnglishFrenchGermanJapaneseSpanishVietnamese
gt
Select LanguageChinese (Simplified)EnglishFrenchGermanJapaneseSpanishVietnamese
MSCULocate UsATMsBranch
MemberSource Credit Union, your member owned financial institution, is committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs and to help you reach your goals. We are equally committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Under federal law, we are required to give you this Privacy Notice. It describes our credit union's Privacy Policy and practices concerning the personal information we collect and disclose about our members. It also includes information about the parties who receive personal and sometimes nonpublic information from us as we conduct the business of the credit union.
Privacy Notice
If you have any questions about this privacy notice, please contact:
MemberSource Credit Union
Attn: Privacy
10100 Richmond Ave.
Houston, Texas 77042
Please see our Data Access Request page to review your information on our site.
Learn more about the full array of financial services enjoyed by MSCU members
CONTACT US
Home >> Privacy Policy
Career Opportunities
Privacy Policy
Website Disclosures
Member Notification
713-627-4000
10100 Richmond Ave.
Houston, Texas 77042
Routing/Transit No: 313084904
MemberSource Credit Union is committed to serving all persons within its field of membership, including those with disabilities. We strive to make not only our physical branches accessible, but also to conform to WCAG 2.0 guidelines for website accessibility. Our efforts are ongoing including frequent testing and updates to improve accessibility. Should you have any problems accessing our branches or website, please call us at 713.627.4000 so we may promptly assist you and remedy any accessibility concerns.
Co-Op Shared Branch
app-store
google-play
allpoint
NCUA
Lender
All Rights Reserved - © MemberSource Credit Union |Site Map
Site By
Loans
Auto/Boat/RVMortgageHE/HIPersonal/Line of CreditSecuredStudentLoan ProtectionRewards DiscountsFinancial CalculatorsMake A PaymentRatesFree Annual Credit ReportLoan brochureApply Now Back
Accounts
Become a MemberBecome a member companySavings AccountsChecking AccountsVisa® Debit CardReorder ChecksChecking ComparisonChecking EssentialsIRAs/CDsRatesInvestmentsYouth AccountsFee ScheduleFinancial Calculators Back
Visa
Visa Credit CardVisa® Debit CardScoreCard RewardsBalance Transfer FormApply Now Back
Electronic Services
Home BankingBill PayMobile BankingeStatementiSnap Deposit CaptureWire InstructionsDirect DepositRouting/Transit No: 313084904 Back
× Close Panel
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you accept these terms.Accept
